export default [
  {
    question: "Which popular Christmas beverage is also called “milk punch?",
    choice1: "Eggnog",
    choice2: "Hot Toddy",
    choice3: "Cranberry-Apple Cider Punch",
    choice4: "Wassail",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "In Home Alone, where are the McCallisters going on vacation when they leave Kevin behind?",
    choice1: "United States of America",
    choice2: "Japan",
    choice3: "Dubai",
    choice4: "Paris",
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "Which country did eggnog come from?",
    choice1: "India",
    choice2: "England",
    choice3: "United States of America",
    choice4: "France",
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "How do you say “Merry Christmas” in Spanish?",
    choice1: "Feliz Navidad",
    choice2: "Felices Fiestas",
    choice3: "Que pases lindo esta navidad",
    choice4: "Mis mejores deseos para esta navidad",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which country started the tradition of putting up a Christmas tree?",
    choice1: "Belgium",
    choice2: "France",
    choice3: "Germany",
    choice4: "Brazil",
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What popular Christmas song was actually written for Thanksgiving?",
    choice1: "Silent Night by Franz Xaver Gruber",
    choice2: "Jingle Bells by James Lord Pierpont",
    choice3: "We Wish You A Merry Christmas by Arthur Sydney Warrell",
    choice4:
      "The Little Drummer Boy by Harry Simeone and Katherine Kennicott Davis",
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Name the first US president who decorated the Christmas tree at the White House",
    choice1: "James Madison",
    choice2: "Franklin Pierce",
    choice3: "Rutherford B Hayes",
    choice4: "John Adams",
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "What does the red color of Christmas symbolize?",
    choice1: "Blood of Jesus",
    choice2: "Santa Claus",
    choice3: "Holly Berries",
    choice4: "Strawberries",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which country sends a huge Christmas tree to London, every year?",
    choice1: "Denmark",
    choice2: "Spain",
    choice3: "Norway",
    choice4: "Netherlands",
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "When is Christmas celebrated in Russia?",
    choice1: "15th December",
    choice2: "15th Feburary",
    choice3: "25th December",
    choice4: "7th January",
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "In which year was Christmas banned in Boston?",
    choice1: "1630",
    choice2: "1659",
    choice3: "1840",
    choice4: "1910",
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which country celebrates its Independence day on Christmas Eve every year?",
    choice1: "Libya",
    choice2: "Syria",
    choice3: "Lebanon",
    choice4: "Algeria",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "How many packages are shipped every year?",
    choice1: "50 million",
    choice2: "210 million",
    choice3: "625 million",
    choice4: "850 million",
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "Which country did St. Nicholas belong to?",
    choice1: "Spain",
    choice2: "Italy",
    choice3: "Greece",
    choice4: "Turkey",
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Which Country celebrates Christmas on 24 December?",
    choice1: "Portugal",
    choice2: "Spain",
    choice3: "United Kingdom",
    choice4: "Australia",
    answer: 1,
  },
];
